globaldelight.com 2019-01-13

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Global Delight Technologies Pvt. Ltd. respects your privacy rights and recognizes the importance of protecting any information collected about you. This Privacy Policy defines how Global Delight collects and uses and shares personal and non-personal information. 

  1. **Collection of Personal/Non-Personal Information you provide us directly:** Profile information that you provide to create account/user profile like your name, email address, address, photo etc. 
  2. **Analytics Information:** We use third-party analytics tools to collect information like the web pages you visit, add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving the product/service. We collect and use this analytics information with analytics information from other users so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify any particular individual User. 
  3. **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Technologies:** We use cookies and other technologies, such as web beacons, web storage, and unique advertising identifiers, to collect information about your activity, browser, and device. We may also use these technologies to collect information when you interact with services we offer through one of our partners, such as advertising and commerce features. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually remove or reject browser cookies through the settings on your browser or device. Keep in mind, though, that removing or rejecting cookies could affect the availability and functionality of our services. To learn more about how we use cookies and your choices, please check out our Cookie Policy. 
  4. **Log Information:** We collect log information when you use our website. That information includes, among other things: 
    1. details about how you’ve used our services.
    2. device information, such as your web browser type and language.
    3. session times.
    4. pages viewed.
    5. IP address.
    6. identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that may uniquely identify your device or browser.
    7. pages you visited before or after navigating to our website.
  5. **Device Identifiers:** We may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more "device identifiers". Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile/desktop device a device identifier may be data stored in connection with network interface and location addressing or data sent to the device by Global Delight.

A device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third-party partner about how you browse and use the service and may help us or others provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled. 

  6. **Metadata:** Metadata is usually technical data that is associated with user content. For example, Metadata can describe how, when and by whom a piece of user content was collected and how that content is formatted. 
  7. **How We Use Information :** The reason we collect your information is to provide you amazing products and services by relentlessly working to improve them. We use your information to: 
    1. develop, operate, improve, deliver, maintain, and protect our products and services.
    2. send you communications, including by email. For example, we may use email to respond to support inquiries or to share information about our products, services, and promotional offers that we think may interest you. 
    3. monitor and analyze trends and usage.
    4. Personalise our services.
    5. contextualize your experience.
    6. provide and improve ad targeting and measurement, including through the use of your precise location information (if you’ve given us permission to collect that information), both on and off our services. 
    7. enhance the safety and security of our products and services.
    8. verify your identity and prevent fraud or other unauthorized or illegal activity.
    9. use information we’ve collected from cookies and other technology to enhance our services and your experience with them.
  8. **Disclosure of Personal/Non-Personal Information:** We may share information about you in the following ways with third parties. 
    1. **With service providers:** We may share information about you with service providers who perform services on our behalf. 
    2. **With business partners:** We may share information about you with business partners that provide services and functionality. 
    3. **With third parties for legal reasons:** We may share information about you if we reasonably believe that disclosing the information is needed to: 
      1. comply with any valid legal process, governmental request, or applicable law, rule, or regulation.
      2. investigate, remedy, or enforce potential Terms of Service violations. 
      3. protect the rights, property, and safety of us, our users, or others.
      4. detect and resolve any fraud or security concerns.
  9. **Data Retention:** Global Delight retains the information collected pursuant to this Privacy Policy. If the collected information is no longer needed for purposes specified in this Privacy Policy, Global Delight shall delete all aforementioned information in its possession. 
  10. **Third-Party Terms and Conditions:** Please note that your access to our website may be subject to certain third-party terms and conditions and privacy policies, including but not limited to application stores, software platforms, and payment processors if any. You recognize and agree that Global Delight is not liable for any such third-party terms and conditions and their use of your personal data.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please feel free to contact us at privacy@globaldelight.com 

  11. **Revisions to Privacy Policy:** We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. But when we do, we’ll let you know one way or another. Sometimes, we’ll let you know by revising the date at the top of the Privacy Policy that’s available on our website and mobile application. Other times, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our websites’ homepages or providing you with an in-app notification).

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please feel free to contact us at privacy@globaldelight.com 

## Cookie Policy

    1. **What are cookies?:** A cookie is a text file stored in a user’s web browser on any device they use to access a website that holds information regarding the user’s visit, such as preferences. When the user returns, the browser provides the cookie with the stored information to the site. 
    2. **What cookies are used for?:** Cookies are used for adjusting a website’s content to fit a user’s preferences and optimize the website. They store useful information that improve the user’s experience of a website. They are most commonly used for: 
      1. Storing login information so that a user does not need to re-login on every visit. 
      2. Recognizing the type of device a user is browsing with and any preferences applied to optimize the website specifically for the device. 
      3. Creating statistics that help website owners to understand how their users interact with their website, which allows them to improve their structure and content. 
    3. **What types of cookies are used?:** There are two types of cookies: persistent cookies and session cookies. 
      1. Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive for a period of time specified in the cookie’s file parameters or until removed manually. When you return to a website and it requires you to login again despite previously storing your login information, it is usually because the persistent cookie expired; this helps to increase security while maintaining accessibility. 
      2. Session cookies, on the other hand, are used temporarily and expire once the website or browser is closed. They are used to track user activity on a website during a single visit. When a website requires that you verify your age or location once every visit before allowing you to view content and without requiring additional personal details, that is a session cookie at work. 
    4. **Do cookies include personal data?:** If there is a need for the collection of personal information, such as for creating accounts, then cookies may store personal information. However, it is required by data protection law that users are informed of the collection of personal data. This data will also be encrypted to render it inaccessible for unauthorized users. 
    5. **Managing cookies:** By default, browsers are configured to accept cookies. However, these settings may be changed to block cookies entirely, or to inform the user each time they are used. Detailed information about cookies and the options associated with them are available in each browsers’ settings. 

Copyright © 2008-2018, Global Delight Technologies Pvt. Ltd. All rights reserved.
